I truly love China,
and I am very fond of Rongcheng.
So rest assured, everyone.
I will increase our investments
to promote trade between China and Japan.
As for profit sharing,
thirty percent for us, seventy for you.
He's really going all out.
President Lian, what do you think?
What does everyone else think?
Doing business with the Japanese is treason, isn't it?
"Trade cooperation"?
What could Japan possibly ship to Rongcheng?
Cotton yarn and silk,
to crush Rongcheng's textile industry?
Or candy and canned goods,
to destroy Rongcheng's food industry?
Or opium and gunpowder,
to destroy our homes in Rongcheng?
President Lian, that's uncalled for.
I am a friendly merchant who loves China.
I'd never harbor such malicious thoughts.
The Japanese slaughtered 300,000 of our compatriots in Nanjing!
Their crimes are heinous,
too numerous to count.
And now you dare try to infiltrate Rongcheng?
Drop your hypocritical act!
As long as I live,
the Matsui Chamber of Commerce
won't lay a single finger on Rongcheng's trade!
Let's go.
Come out.
You didn't kill anyone.
Why run?
And wait for you to drag me to the police station?
We at the police department aren't that stupid.
Who the killer is
is plain as day.
You went to the Sanshan Gang.
Find anything?
Your Sanshan Gang
seems to have let some vermin slip in.
What do you really want from me?
I want to
catch a rat in a trap.
Mr. Matsui.
Long time no see.
Instead of running for your life,
what are you doing here?
I'm here to finish this game of chess with you.
Very well.
Since you're so eager to lose,
I'll gladly oblige.
The one who shot at me three years ago,
and the one who killed
Deputy Director Zhou half a year ago...
It was you, wasn't it?
You're tougher to kill than Zhou Kun.
Creating a diversion,
assassinating Mr. He, the overseas Chinese,
and sending me away from the Sanshan Gang...
It was all to give the killer
a chance to assassinate Chief Hu, wasn't it?
That's right.
I'm curious, though.
How did you convince Zhuang Liancheng?
Hall Master Zhuang,
are you truly content
spending your life under Lian Ye,
even calling him Chief one day?
You're his equal,
yet you outshine him at every turn.
Soon, the Japanese army will advance in force,
and Rongcheng will be ours for the taking.
If Hall Master Zhuang helps the Japanese army,
your rise to power will be right around the corner.
I'm at Mr. Matsui's command.
When did you
realize Zhuang Liancheng was the killer?
The first to realize Zhuang Liancheng was the killer
wasn't me.
It was Hu Baozhu.
The stab wound on the Chief's body
slanted from bottom right to top left,
proving the killer was left-handed.
And I'm right-handed.
Baozhu knew at a glance I wasn't the killer.
So the next day, when she went to Club Jasmine...
Lian Ye, you listen to me!
If Hall Master Zhuang hadn't told us
my father lost his temper meeting the Japanese,
and if we hadn't gone to comfort him
and exposed your scheme,
you really would've gotten away with it!
Making everyone believe
that I was the one who killed the Chief.
Killing two birds with one stone,
to drive me out of the Sanshan Gang.
Between Zhuang Liancheng and Hu Baozhu,
whose throwing daggers are deadlier?
Baozhu,
what's the meaning of this?
I'm here to avenge my father, of course.
You think I murdered the Chief?
Where's your proof?
Come out!
Hall Master Lian, the Chief asks for you.
It was Hall Master Zhuang
who told me to notify Hall Master Lian
to meet with the Chief alone.
My father's wound showed
the killer was left-handed. It was you
who caught him off guard and killed him!
Go join your father!
So what if you killed Zhuang Liancheng?
My men have already infiltrated the Sanshan Gang.
Has fortune arrived?
I-It's arrived.
N-No, it hasn't.
Did you think the Sanshan Gang...
...was so easy to infiltrate?
Has fortune arrived?
F-Fortune has always been here!
I know what you're afraid of.
Come here.
Question them dock by dock.
If the secret code is wrong,
execute them immediately.
Yes, sir! Right away!
Move!
I already told Wang Dali
to pass the secret code to our Sanshan Gang brothers.
Any Pingtan refugee entering the Sanshan Gang
who doesn't know the code
will be executed on the spot.
Sachiko.
Clean the room and toss this trash far away.
Yes, sir.
Even if you kill our men, it's too late.
After tonight,
all of you will be prisoners of the Japanese!
You kept checking the clock just now.
Were you waiting for ten o'clock,
when the Japanese army launches their night raid?
To storm the city?
We already interrogated your Japanese spies.
We know all about your plan to strike from both inside and out.
That signal flare just now...
wasn't fired by a Japanese spy.
My men fired it.
So what?
The Major General has mobilized overwhelming forces,
more than enough to take Rongcheng!
Don't you forget,
Li Mingyuan is no pushover.
Well fought!
Mingyuan,
how did you know
the Japanese would launch a night raid tonight?
While investigating a case,
I ran into some Pingtan refugees.
Their accents didn't sound like Pingtan locals,
sounding more like Japanese instead.
I looked into it and found out
that Japanese agents
were posing as Pingtan refugees
to infiltrate the Sanshan Gang.
So I captured a Japanese spy and interrogated him.
That Japanese spy
confessed to tonight's night raid.
Thanks to your timely intel this time,
we caught the Japanese in one fell swoop
and spared Rongcheng
from the flames of war.
General...